♪♪～
I see. I understand your circumstances in Kou.
（シンドバッド）なるほどね。　君と
煌帝国の事情は　よく分かったよ。
I am prepared to risk my life to gain your trust.
（白龍）
あなたの信用を得るためには→
命を懸ける覚悟です。
To that end, I have laid all of my cards out on the table.
そのために俺は　すべてを隠さず→
打ち明けました。→
King Sinbad, please lend me your power in the fight against the Kou Empire.
シンドバッド王よ
どうか　ご協力ください→
煌帝国との戦いに。
（シンドバッド）
君は　留学に来たんだろ？→
You came here to study, right?
Then first, I want you to take the time to study my country.
まずは　ゆっくりと
この国を見てほしいものだ。
I don't have time for that!
そんな時間は　ないのです。
今すぐ返答を…　あっ！
Please give me your answer-
♪♪～
（シンドバッド）話の続きがしたければ
もっと学びなさい。→
If you wish to continue our discussion, become more knowledgeable.
Learn about the outside world, and the various people who inhabit it.
外の世界のことを…→
そこに住む
さまざまな人々のことを。→
Actually, there's someone I'd like you to meet.
それには　まず
君に会ってほしい人物がいるな。→
Alibaba Saluja.
アリババ・サルージャ。→
The third prince of a country occupied by Kou, Balbadd.
煌帝国が占領した
あのバルバッド王国の第三王子だ。
♪♪～
miwatasu kagiri no kouya ni hitori tatteirunda
In the wilderness, as far as the eye can see, stands a lone figure
sorya miburui mo surun darou
Surely he trembles as he stands
♪♪～
osanai shoujo ga yume ni miteiru hakuba no ouji mitaina mono
A young girl dreams of a prince on a white horse
♪♪～
bokura mo dokka de shiranai uchi ni kitai shiteshimatteitano kamo
Unwittingly, we also fall to such dreams of perfection
fukanzen na kono sekai wo dareka ga
No one will recreate
♪♪～
kakitashite kureru nante nai
this imperfect world for us
♪♪～
shinjiru toiu kotoba wo kimi ha kodomoppoi to warau kai?
Will you call me naïve if I say that I still dream?
miwatasu kagiri no kouya de yukisaki wo shimesu mono
In the wilderness, as far as the eye can see, shines a guiding light
♪♪～
mune ni daite aruitekou sekai ga hohoemu
Hold it close as you go and the world will smile upon you
kono basho ga doko darou to miagereba mabataku hoshi
If you're lost, consult the twinkling stars
♪♪～
sono shita de kimi wo omoeba warukunai yoru ni naru
If I think of you while gazing at those stars, the night brightens
tsumetai mune ni hi ga tomoru
and a warm fire lights in my heart
This guy here's actually a prince! Can you tell?
（シャルルカン）でさ　こいつ
こう見えて　王子だったんだぜ。
20th Night
The Two Princes
Wait, really?
ええ～　ほんとに～？
見えな～い。　けど　かわいい～！
I can't! But he's cute!
Teacher, don't you think you've had a bit too much to drink?
（アリババ）
師匠　ちょっと飲み過ぎなんじゃ…。
（シャルルカン）「師匠」じゃねぇ！
飲み屋じゃ→
Don't call me teacher when we're out drinking! Use Shar!
シャルさんと呼べ　シャルさんと。
はぁ…。
（シャルルカン）
それより　お前は　どうなんだよ？
Anyway, as a former prince, what do you think?
元王子として。
はっ？
Huh?
（シャルルカン）「はっ？」じゃねぇよ。
あの煌帝国の皇子のことを→
Don't huh me.
I'm asking you what you think about that Kou prince.
どう思うかって聞いてんだよ。
いや　どうって言われても…。
I don't really know...
I want to have a match with him.
俺は　一度　手合わせしてみてぇ。→
まっ　剣術は
俺の方が　上だろうけどな。
But I'm sure my swordplay is better than his.
うっ！
And I've been with finer women than him too!
（シャルルカン）あっ　もちろん
抱いた女の数もな。　ははっ！
もう　やだ～！
≪シャルちゃんったら～！
Don't say that.
Oh Shar!
（シャルルカン）ほら！
そっちのおねえさんも　こっち来て。
Hey babe, why don't you come closer?
きゃあ～！
ふふふっ　お邪魔しま～す。
Don't mind if I do!
（シャルルカン）えっ？
いいよ　いいよ　邪魔しちゃって。
I was waiting for that!
Is that seat open?
（エカテリーナ）お隣　よろしいかしら？
んん…。
Is your arm injured?
（エカテリーナ）
その腕　ケガでもされたのですか？
いえ　なんでもありません。
No, it's nothing.
Just a manly battle wound.
ちょっとした　男の勲章ですよ。
My name is Ekaterina.
（エカテリーナ）
エカテリーナでございます。
（シャルルカン）
やめろって！　スベスベだなぁ。
Stop that! Oh your skin is so smooth!
（ヤムライハ）「シャラール・バラク」！
Sharrar Baraq!
（アラジン）あっ！
How was that protective magic, Miss Yamu?
どうだい？　ヤムおねえさん。
今の防壁魔法は。
I put together two commands: gather the flames and create a wall.
炎を集める　壁を作る→
２つの命令式を
組み合わせてみたよ。
Pretty good.
なかなかいいわね。　でも　そこに→
But if you add just one more command, you could turn that into offensive magic.
あと１つ　命令式を加えれば
攻撃魔法にもなるのよ。
あっ！
うふふっ。
うっ！
（ヤムライハ）ふふっ　どう？
What about that?
Amazing, Miss Yamu!
すごいよ　ヤムさん。
I want to try that with fire!
僕は　それを
炎でやってみたいんだ。
キン！　キン　キン！
What's the matter?
（シャルルカン）おら　おら！　どうした!?
キン　キン　キン！
You call that swordplay?
なんだ？　その太刀筋は！
This guy is completely different when he's holding a sword!
（心の声）
≪この人　剣術の修行のときだけ→
人が変わり過ぎる≫
うっ！　くっ…。　くそっ！
Dammit...
（シャルルカン）全然ダメだな。
はぁ　はぁ…。
That was terrible.
Your Djinn equip weapon doesn't fit your sword-fighting style at all.
その武器化魔装
お前の剣術に合ってねぇよ。
（シャルルカン）だけど　まあ　落ち込むな。
But don't worry.
There's a better way for you to do this.
お前に合った
もっといい　やり方がある。
What do you mean?
もっといい　やり方って？
なんでも　聞けば
すぐに解決すると思うなよ。
Answers won't come just because you asked for them.
What?
ええ～？
（シャルルカン）今日は　ここまで。→
We're done for today.
Use your head and think about what I said.
まずは
自分の頭で　考えてみるんだな。
はぁ～…。
ん？
元気出しなよ　アリババくん。
Cheer up, Alibaba.
僕も　さっき　ヤムさんに
たっぷりと　いたぶられたところさ。
I was bullied around by Miss Yamu the whole time.
You have it tough too.
お前も　大変だな。
But it's great! I'm learning so much!
でも　いろいろ教えてもらって
楽しいよ。
あっ　モルさんだ。
It's Morg! She's back from the studio!
町の工房から　戻ってきたんだ。
（アラジン　アリババ）おお～！
Wow!
This is your household vessel?!
これが　モルジアナの眷属器か。
（モルジアナ）はい。
Correct.
足飾りにしてもらいました。
I had them create anklets for me.
模様は
暗黒大陸で信仰されている→
The pattern is a fire bird. It's the symbol of the sun according to the beliefs of the Dark Continent.
太陽の象徴　火の鳥だそうです。
きれいだね。
早速　使ってみせてよ。
They're pretty!
Try them on!
♪♪～
The chains look so pretty!
鎖も　きれいになったねぇ。
They look more like the decorations dancers wear!
鎖っていうより
踊り子の人たちの→
飾りに似てるなぁ。
モルさん　早く見せて。
Morg, show us what you can do!
あっ…　うん。
はあ～！
（２人）おお～！
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
すみません　すみません！
Are you sure it wouldn't be better without the chains?
その鎖
ない方がいいんじゃないのか？
What if you wore them somewhere other than your ankles?
それとも
足じゃない所に付けるか？
う～ん…。
≪どこに付けても　これは
ただの　きれいな飾りだわ≫
No matter where I wear them, these are nothing but decorations.
I don't know how to use them in battle.
≪戦いに
どう使えばいいのか分からない≫
How would you like to use them?
モルさんは　どう使いたいんだい？
えっ　私？
Me?
Miss Yamu said that the first step to creating new magic is figuring out what you want that magic to do.
ヤムさんが　言ってたんだ。
新しい魔法を作るときは→
まず
これから　どんなことがしたいか→
楽しく考えるんだって。
I think creating a household vessel is the same.
眷属器の能力も
きっと　同じなんじゃないかな。
What I want to do...
私のしたいこと…。
♪♪～
I want the strength to help the two of you.
私は　お二人の役に立てるような
強さが欲しいです。
You're already more than strong enough, Morgiana!
モルジアナは　もう　十分強いよ。
うん　うん。
He's right!
あっ　でも　あれは助かったな。
You know what was really helpful? That time when you threw me.
俺を　ぶん投げてくれた　あれ。
Without you, there's no way I could've fought against enemies in the air.
モルジアナがいなけりゃ
空中の敵と　戦えなかった。
You saved me too.
僕も　助けてもらったよ。
ビュンビュン飛んで
運んでくれたよね。
You jumped really fast and took me away from danger!
You're amazing, Morg. When you're around, it's like we have wings!
すごいね～。　モルさんがいると→
僕たち
羽が生えたみたいになっちゃうね。
I'm your... wings?
私が　お二人の羽？
Wow!
すご～い！
強～い！
So strong!
I understand.
分かりました。
ちょっと待て。　今　何を考えた？
Wait, what did you just imagine?
Excuse me for interrupting.
≫（白龍）
お話しのところ　失礼します。
I have been searching for the three of you at King Sinbad's request.
シンドバッド王の命を受けまして
お三方を捜しておりました。
I'm just accompanying him.
（紅玉）私は　ただの付き添いよ。
What does King Sinbad want?
シンドバッドさんの命令って？
（白龍）はい。
三人のもとに付いて　共に行動し→
He ordered me to accompany the three of you, do what you do, and learn from you all.
彼らから学べと。　今日から
どうか　よろしくお願いします。
I hope we can work together.
あっ…。
（白龍）あなたが　マギですね。→
You're the Magi, right?
Thank you for helping my sister, Hakuei, on the Kouga plains.
黄牙の草原で
姉　白瑛が　お世話になりました。
あっ。
（白龍）姉を救ってくださり→
I am very grateful to you!
本当に　感謝しています。
Is she doing well?
お姉さんは　元気かい？
（白龍）はい。→
Yes. She is currently on campaign in the western part of the Tenzan Plateau.
今は　天山西部へ
遠征に出ております。
She has gathered the people of Kouga and is continuing negotiations with other tribes.
黄牙の民を連れ
他民族へ　交渉を続けております。
（紅玉）怖い目。
あっ。
What a scary look.
えっ？　あっ…　その…。
A-Ah, um-!
（紅玉）バルバッドでは
お互い　いろいろあったけど→
I am aware that a lot occurred back in Balbadd, but
should we not declare a truce for the moment being?
今は　ひとまず
休戦するべきでなくって？
Yeah. Fighting won't get us anywhere!
そうだね。　ケンカしても
なんにもならないし。
I agree. Let's let bygones be bygones and work together.
そうよ。　あのときのことは
水に流して　仲よくしましょ。
い…　痛いじゃないか！
そっちこそ　痛いじゃない！
O-Ow, that hurts!
You're the one who's hurting me!
You're stabbing me!
刺さってる　刺さってる！
離しなさいよ！
Let go of me!
Sorry about that, Hakuryuu.
ごめんな　白龍。　あいつ
ちょっと　バルバッドで　あってさ。
They have some history from Balbadd.
Is that not true for you as well?
（白龍）それは　あなたも同じでは？
えっ？
Sir Alibaba Saluja. You too surely harbor hatred inside your heart.
（白龍）アリババ・サルージャ殿→
あなたも　内心は
憎んでおられるのでしょう？→
Hatred for me as the prince of the
country that has occupied Balbadd.
占領国の皇子である　俺のことを。
い…　いや　俺は　もう…。
N-No, I'm already-
うっ！
無理をされずともよい。
You do not need to force yourself.
It is the truth that the Kou Empire tried to occupy Balbadd,
それだけのことを
煌帝国は　貴国にした。
そして　今も　しようとしている。
and that they are still trying to do so now.
あっ　俺は…。
I...
（アリババの声）憎め！
Hate him!
（紅玉）ひぃ～…。
あっ　アリババくん？
Alibaba?
The governor-general who has been dispatched to lead the second expedition into Balbadd
バルバッド国に　西征総督として
派遣されているのは→
煌帝国第一皇子
炎帝こと　練紅炎です。
is the First Imperial Prince, Kouen Ren, also known as Entei.
Hate him. Kill him. Hate him! Kill him!
（アリババの声）
憎め。　殺せ。　憎め。　殺せ。
He will use Balbadd's insurrection as a stepping stone for conquest.
ううっ…。
（白龍）バルバッドの内乱は→
その踏み台にされたのです。
アリババさん？
Alibaba?
During Balbadd's insurrection, you lost a dear friend, did you not?
That's right, more hatred! Kill him!
（アリババの声）
そうだ　もっと憎め。　もっと殺せ！
（白龍）友人を
亡くされたのではないですか？
You do not need to hide such emotions.
ならば
その気持ち　隠すことなどなく…。
ううっ！
あっ　アリババ殿？
Sir Alibaba?
くっ！　ぐわぁ～！　ああっ…。
あぁ…　ああっ！　ううっ…　ぐっ！
うぅ…。　くっ…　ううっ！
≫ガチャ（扉の音）
What happened?
何があった!?
あっ…　シンドバッドさん。
King Sinbad.
It's okay. My arm just hurts a little-
大丈夫です。
ただ　ちょっと　腕が…　うっ！
We pushed you that much yet you still won't budge?
（イスナーンの声）
これだけ唆しても　動かぬか。
♪♪～
What a spineless man.
（イスナーン）
まったく　意気地のない男だ。
You're-!
お前は…。
（イスナーン）だが→
But thanks to you, I was able to get past the barrier and enter Sindria.
おかげで　結界を越え
シンドリアに入ることができた。
（シンドバッド）ふん！
♪♪～
ふっ！　マギだけ気付いたか。
Only the Magi noticed what was happening?
なんだ？　この血は。
What is this blood?
（イスナーン）もう遅い。
我らが父の意志による→
It's too late.
I have done as our father ordered and cursed you to death.
死の呪縛を施した。
Consider it an invitation from us,
first-class singularity, King Sinbad,
それは　我々からの招待状だよ。
第一級特異点　シンドバッド王→
and King Candidate chosen from
Solomon's arrogance, King Alibaba.
そして　ソロモンの傲慢に
選ばれし器　アリババ王よ。→
Become black kings and surrender to our father.
黒き王となり
我が父のもとへ下れ。→
The curse has attached itself to your magoi flow and will slowly turn all of your rukh black.
それは　お前たちの
魔力の気脈に取りつき→
ルフを　黒く染めていく。
After that, you will be reborn as a completely different person.
やがて　まったく別の人間に
生まれ変わるだろう。
それ　すなわち堕転。
堕転？
In other words, you will have fallen into depravity.
Fallen into depravity?
You cannot escape it.
（イスナーン）
逆らわないことだ。　あらがえば→
If you fight it, Solomon's rukh and the black rukh will
destroy each other inside your body and your body will die.
ソロモンのルフと黒いルフが
己の中で殺し合い→
肉体は　死に絶えるだろう。
（２人）あっ。
I'll be waiting for you in the darkness of depravity.
（イスナーン）堕転の闇で　待っているよ。
♪♪～
≪どうすりゃいいんだ。
シンドバッドさんまで…≫
What should we do? Even King Sinbad was infected!
There's no need to worry.
気に病む必要はない。
呪いなどというものは存在せん。→
Curses do not exist.
これは　魔法の一種だ。　そうだろ？
This is a type of magic.
Right?
Yes. This black mark is moving because of magic.
（ヤムライハ）はい。　この黒いアザ
魔力で作動しています。
If it's magic, then that means there's a way to get rid of it, right?
魔法なら
必ず　解き方があるはずだよね？
But I've never seen this type of magic before.
でも　こんな魔法　見たことがない。
What kind of commands is it working under?
一体　どんな命令式で
動いているのか…。
複雑な魔法の解き方は
かけた本人にしか分からない。
With complicated magic, only the caster knows how to remove it.
No...
そんな…。
あっ。
There is one way.
一つだけ　可能性がある。
それは　どんな？
What is it?
Even farther south than here lies an island of the Toran people. On that island is a dungeon.
ここより　更に南
トラン族の住む島に　迷宮がある。
あっ。
（シンドバッド）攻略すれば→
It's the 61st dungeon, Zagan, which, if conquered, can heal any wound or illness.
どんな傷や病も　癒やす力を
得ることができるという→
第６１迷宮ザガン。
The djinn there could be our saving grace.
そこに住むジンならば
俺たちを救ってくれるかもしれん。
Would you like to bet on it, Alibaba?
その可能性に賭けてみるか？
アリババ君。
Yes.
はい。
（シンドバッド）俺も行く…→
I would like to go with you, but I cannot.
と言いたいところだが
それが不可能でな。→
君たちだけで行けるか？
Can you go by yourselves?
（３人）あっ。
どういうことですか？
Why not?
If me or anyone in my household tries to pass through a dungeon's gate, we'll simply slip through and nothing will happen.
（シンドバッド）俺や　俺の眷族が
迷宮の聖門を通ろうとすると→
すり抜けるだけで　何も起きん。→
俺が　７人目のジンと
契約した時点で　こうなった。
This happened when I made a contract with my seventh djinn.
７人目のジンは　「お前には
もう十分だろう」と言っていた。
My seventh djinn said to me, that's enough for you.
A metal vessel user can most likely only gain a certain amount of power.
（ジャーファル）おそらく
力を得過ぎた金属器使いには→
それ以上
力を与えられないのでしょう。
I understand. We'll go ourselves!
分かりました。
俺たちだけで　やってみます。
And we'll definitely break this curse.
そして
必ず　この呪いを解いてみせる。
Please allow me to join you.
（白龍）俺も　同行させてください。
（３人）あっ。
I did ask you to learn from those three, but I didn't count on conquering a dungeon.
確かに　この三人に付いて
学べと言ったが→
迷宮攻略となれば　話は別だ。
相当の危険を伴う。
It will be a dangerous journey.
I am aware and ready.
覚悟のうえです。
俺は　かねてより→
I have long wanted to conquer a dungeon and have been searching for a Magi to do just that.
迷宮攻略を望み　マギを捜していた。
I heard that the Magi Judal was in the Kou Empire and that he was more than happy to guide Kou's leaders to a dungeon.
しかし　煌帝国は
すでに　マギたるジュダルがおり→
各将を　迷宮に
斡旋していると聞いたが。
（白龍）
いえ　彼の力だけは　どうしても→
No, I absolutely do not want to use his power.
借りるわけにはまいりません。
（シンドバッド）
だろうな。　よし　同行を認めよう。
I see.
Very well, you may join them.
（白龍）ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much!
♪♪～
≫（ピスティ）そんな深刻な顔して
あんまり思い詰めると→
If you think so hard and frown so much, you won't be able to gather your strength when you need it!
いざってとき
十分な力を　発揮できないぞ。
But it's my fault...
でも　俺のせいで…。
Don't worry about Sin.
シンなら大丈夫。
それに　ヤムの停滞魔法で→
Yamu's stagnation magic can prevent the
curse from spreading for around ten days.
１０日ほどだけど
死の呪縛の発動を→
抑えることができたし。
ああ…。
Yeah...
Be careful.
（ヤムライハ・回想）((注意してね。
アリババ君の魔力の量なら→
I don't think this will be a problem with the amount of magoi you have,
問題ないとは思うけど
激しく金属器を使うと→
but if you use your metal vessel strongly, you could break the seal.
封印が壊れる可能性があるから))
My amount of magoi?
((俺ならって…
じゃあ　シンドバッドさんは？))
What about King Sinbad?
He can't use his magoi at all for a little while.
((しばらくは　絶対に
使わないように言ってあるわ))
((あっ))
≫グワァーー！
あっ！
ドーン！
（一同）おおっ！
（乗組員）くそっ！　出やがった！
（乗組員）来るぞ！
≫ザザー！
（２人）あっ！
グワァーー！
（一同）おおっ…。
（２人）くっ！
≪（ピスティ）私に任せて！
（２人）ん？
Leave him to me!
ピィーー（笛の音）
≫ピィーー
グルルル…
♪♪～
Good boy. You're such a good boy!
よしよし。　お前は素直ないい子だ。
Go back to the ocean now.
さあ　海へ　お帰り。
♪♪～
おお～！
ははははっ！
（３人）あぁ…。
さっすが　ピスティ様！
You're amazing, Mistress Pisti!
さすが～！　はははっ。
ピスティ様！
I can use my rukh to match the wavelength of my voice and my flute to speak to animals.
（ピスティ）私は　笛の音や声で
ルフの波長を合わせて→
動物たちと
友達になることができるんだよ。
Thanks! Um... Pisti?
ありがとう　ピスティ…　ちゃん？
（ピスティ）あっ。　ええ～？
私のことも　ヤムみたく→
Aw, can't you call me Miss, like you call Miss Yamu?
おねえさんって
呼んでくれないの？
ん？　おねえさんなのかい？
Miss?
Yeah! I'm older than Alibaba!
うん。
私　アリババ君より年上だよ。
（２人）ええ～！
What?!
You're so rude.
（ピスティ）
失礼だなぁ。　こう見えても→
No matter what I look like, I'm still older than you.
私　おねえさんだし
君たちよりは　いろいろと→
And I am much more experienced than you guys in many different areas.
経験も豊富なんだぞ～。
んん～…。
♪♪～
おねい…　さん？
...Miss?
ひどい！　アラジン君！
You're such a jerk, Aladdin!
（一同）ははははっ！
Man, why do guys like big girls so much?
（ピスティ）あぁ～あ…
どうして　こう　男の人って→
タプタプしてる女の子の方が
好きなんだろうね～？
あっ　はあ…　そうなんでしょうか。
Do they?
（ピスティ）そうだよ！　ここが…。
≫（白龍）皆さん→
Yeah! Big, bouncy girls!
Everyone, food is ready.
≫食事が出来ましたよ。
あっ。
Wow!
うわっ　すごい！
You have all been so kind to me. I thought I could at least cook you a meal in thanks.
（白龍）お世話になってばかりでは
落ち着かず→
せめて　料理ぐらいはと。
Did you make all of this, Mister Hakuryuu?
これ　全部　おにいさんが作ったの？
My sister taught me that I must be able to perform all of my everyday tasks myself.
身の回りのことは　なんでも
自分でできるようになれと→
姉に仕込まれまして。
そっか～。→
I see! You'll make a great husband one day.
君は　将来　いい旦那様になるよ。
煌帝国の皇子様と聞いて→
He's very different from the person I imagined when I heard "prince of the Kou Empire".
想像していた人とは
だいぶ違いました。
はうっ。
ああ…　そうだな。
Ye-Yeah, he is.
Hate him. Kill him.
（アリババの声）憎め。　殺せ。
((あのとき　確かに
俺の耳に　そうささやく声が→
I'm sure that I heard a voice whisper in my ear.
聞こえたんです))
It must be the voice of that man
who cursed us trying to tempt you.
（シンドバッド）((それは　あの男が
君を唆そうとした声だろう？))
But it also might be my conscience telling me what I really think.
((だけど　もしかすると　俺の→
本当の
心の声だったのかもしれない))
That's why I'm uneasy about the idea of traveling with him.
((だから　あいつを同行させるのは
不安なんです))
（シンドバッド）((君なら　大丈夫だ))
((でも…))
You'll be okay.
But!
Even if, in some deep part of your heart, you hate him enough to want to kill him,
((たとえ
心の奥底で　彼を殺したいほど→
憎んでいたとしても
それを乗り越え　許すこともまた→
you must learn to overcome that and forgive him. It's another test for you.
今の君に与えられた試練だ))
はうっ！　んん～！
（ジャーファル）その呪い
あなたなら　かわせたはず。
You should've been able to avoid that curse.
It provides more motivation for them if I'm also cursed.
（シンドバッド）俺も染まってた方が
彼らも　やる気になる。
Sin!
シン！
（シンドバッド）それに→
And also, if Al-Thamen is after them, they'll be safer inside the dungeon.
アル・サーメンが
彼らを狙っているならば→
逆に　迷宮の中にいた方が
安全だとも言える。
♪♪～
This place is much more lively than I thought it'd be.
思ったより　にぎわってるんだな。
（白龍）トランの民…
本で読んだことはあるけど→
I've read about the Toran people in my studies before, but this is my first time seeing them in person.
実際に見るのは　初めてだ。
おっととと…。　あっ→
I'm sorry!
ごめんなさい。
だから　無理するなって言っただろ。
I told you take it slowly!
♪♪～
What's the matter?
（ピスティ）どうしたの？
あっ　いや…。
No, nothing...
（ティアレ）あの…　皆さん→
E-Excuse me.
A-Are you going to the dungeon?
これから
迷宮に行かれるんですか？
Yes?
（白龍）そうだけど。
だったら　お願いです。
Then I have a request!
Please take me with you!
私も　一緒に連れていってください。
I want to save my parents!
父と母を助けたいんです。
Did your parents... ?
（ピスティ）もしかして　ご両親を…。
What are you talking about?
どういうことだい？
（ピスティ）ほかの迷宮と違い→
Unlike other dungeons, supposedly Zagan eats people.
ザガンは
人を食らうといわれているの。
Eats people?
人を？
そう。
Yes. The story is that those who approach Zagan are dragged in and devoured.
迷宮に近づく者を
自ら引きずり込んで→
食べてしまうって。
この島の人たちも→
I've heard that a number of the people on this island have fallen to Zagan.
もう何人も
ザガンに食べられたと聞くわ。
No one's tried to approach the dungeon since.
（ティアレ）今では　誰も
迷宮に近づこうとしません。→
Everyone says the people who were swallowed are dead.
飲み込まれた人たちは死んだって
みんな　言います。
That's why I have to be the one to save my parents!
だから　私が
父と母を助けるしかないんです。
Please take me with you!
お願いします。
私も一緒に　連れていってください。
ダメだ。　君は　足手まといになる。
We can't. You'll hold us back.
We can't bring you along.
連れていくわけにはいかない。
（ティアレ）でも　助けたいんです！
But I want to save them!
♪♪～
はぁ～　でも…。
But...
I understand. I will save them for you.
（白龍）分かった。　それじゃあ　俺が
君の代わりに　それをやろう。
おい！
あっ。
Hey!
I will definitely find your parents for you.
必ず　君の両親を捜し出す。
If they're dead, I will defeat everything that lives in that dungeon.
もし死んでいても　俺が
迷宮に巣くう　すべてを倒す。
All right?
それで　どうだ？
♪♪～
Hakuryuu...
白龍…。
あっ　モルさん
腕に付けることにしたんだね。
Wow, Morg! You decided to wear them as bracelets?
Yes. I don't know what to do with them yet though.
はい。　まだ　何もできませんが。
≪許すことも　また試練…　か≫
Learning to forgive him is another test.
ん？
あっ…。
I see something! Is that Zagan?
見えてきた！
あれが　ザガンじゃないかな。
あっ　なんでしょうか？　今のは。
What was that light just now?
That might be the entrance.
あそこに　入り口があるのかも。
な…　なんだ!?
W-What's happening?
あっ！
アラジン！
Aladdin!
うわぁ～～！
ああ～！
あっ！
（白龍）くっ！
ぐわぁ～！
≪この感じ　知ってる≫
I know this feeling!
♪♪～
くっ！
I'm back.
≪また　ここに来たんだ≫
I will definitely pass this test!
≪この試練
絶対に乗り越えてみせる！≫
♪♪～
"kimi ni ha yuuki ga aru"
"You're a hero."
sono hitokoto wo shinji tobidashita
Off you went, believing in those words
mawari ha kare wo waratte
While those around you mocked you
♪♪～
"douse nani hitotsu aitsu ni ha dekinai sa"
"Let him go. He can't do anything."
iwaseteoke
Let them talk
kimi ha keshite yowaku nanka nai
You're far from weak
dare ni mo hatasenakatta yume wo negae tsuyoku
Believe in those dreams no one else could reach!
♪♪～
dare ni mo hatasenakatta yume wo negae tsuyoku
Believe in those dreams no one else could reach!
kanarazu kanaete miserutte
You'll definitely make them come true
♪♪～
saa mizukara no hata kakage
Come, fly your own flag
susume mae ni
and keep moving forward
nijimu namida ha
The tears you shed
kimi no akashi
are proof that you're alive
♪♪～
chikara ni narou
Draw strength from your tears!
mayou toki ha kono boku ga soba ni iru
When you are in trouble, I will be by your side
dakara ikou
So go!
♪♪～
sekai no subete wo mi ni
And see the world
Welcome to my living dungeon.
In reality, you hate me as well!
Why are you so stubborn?
Next time: The Dungeon Zagan
21th Night
The Dungeon Zagan
You are not alone.
政府が次の日銀総裁として
黒田東彦アジア開発銀行総裁を
起用する方針を固め
副総裁人事と併せて最終調整に入
ったことが
ＪＮＮの取材で明らかになった。